https://urnseller.com/privacy-policy/

Home / Privacy Policy
Welcome to our Privacy Policy
Our website address is: https://urnseller.com.
It is Urnseller.com, Inc.’s policy to respect your privacy
regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. This
Privacy Policy applies to www.urnseller.com (hereinafter, “us”,
“we”, or “www.urnseller.com”). We respect your privacy and
are committed to protecting personally identifiable information you may provide
us through the Website. We have adopted this privacy policy (“Privacy
Policy”) to explain what information may be collected on our Website, how
we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the
information to third parties. This Privacy Policy applies only to information
we collect through the Website and does not apply to our collection of
information from other sources.
This Privacy Policy, together with the Terms and conditions
posted on our Website, set forth the general rules and policies governing your
use of our Website. Depending on your activities when visiting our Website, you
may be required to agree to additional terms and conditions.
Website Visitors
Like most website operators, Urnseller.com, Inc. collects
non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and
servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language
preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request.
Urnseller.com, Inc.’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying
information is to better understand how Urnseller.com, Inc.’s visitors use its
website. From time to time, Urnseller.com, Inc. may release non-personally-identifying
information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the
usage of its website.
Urnseller.com, Inc. also collects potentially
personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for
logged in users and for users leaving comments on https://urnseller.com blog
posts. Urnseller.com, Inc. only discloses logged in user and commenter IP
addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses
personally-identifying information as described below.
Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information
Certain visitors to Urnseller.com, Inc.’s websites choose to interact with Urnseller.com, Inc. in ways that require Urnseller.com, Inc. to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Urnseller.com, Inc. gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for a blog at https://urnseller.com to provide a username and email address.
Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Advertisements
Ads appearing on our website may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Urnseller.com, Inc. and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
Cookies
To enrich and perfect your online experience, Urnseller.com,
Inc. uses “Cookies”, similar technologies and services provided by
others to display personalized content, appropriate advertising and store your
preferences on your computer.
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on
a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website
each time the visitor returns. Urnseller.com, Inc. uses cookies to help
Urnseller.com, Inc. identify and track visitors, their usage of
https://urnseller.com, and their website access preferences. Urnseller.com,
Inc. visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should
set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Urnseller.com, Inc.’s
websites, with the drawback that certain features of Urnseller.com, Inc.’s
websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
By continuing to navigate our website without changing your
cookie settings, you hereby acknowledge and agree to Urnseller.com, Inc.’s use
of cookies.
E-commerce
Those who engage in transactions with Urnseller.com, Inc. – by purchasing Urnseller.com, Inc.’s services or products, are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Urnseller.com, Inc. collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Urnseller.com, Inc.. Urnseller.com, Inc. does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.
Privacy Policy Changes
Although most changes are likely to be minor, Urnseller.com, Inc. may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Urnseller.com, Inc.’s sole discretion. Urnseller.com, Inc. encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
Search for:
Recent Posts
California sues cremation company, claims it swindled customers
